Now, it's important to remember that we're
not here to teach you how to
build a weather app.
It's not even to teach you all the Android
APIs that we use to build it.
It's really about retraining your brain to
start thinking like a mobile developer,
which is really important, because at the
end of this course we're gonna ask you to
build your own final project.
[NOISE].
We're expecting you to already be familiar
with object-oriented programming, and
to have experience with Java or a similar
language.
Personally, I got started with Android
after years of Delphi and C# development.
As engineers, we're trained to map our
experiences in one language or
SDK into new ones.
Looking for patterns and shortcuts we can
get up to speed as quickly as possible.
But mobile, and Android in particular,
have some fundamental differences that
mean some of our experience and
intuition will actually make us worse
mobile engineers.
We like to think of Smartphones as
computers that fit into our pockets.
In a way that's true, but the computers
from the 90s,
like this Powerhouse I was using nearly 20
years ago.
With limited internet connectivity, low
speed CPUs, and
limited RAM, on top of which, they're all
running on batteries.
As we go through the course,
I'll be returning to each of these key
mobile challenges.
Looking for places where you're
experienced on desktop or
server, or even other mobile platforms
might lead you in the wrong direction.
I will also be back to tell you some
stories from the early days of Android.
Stories that describe how the Android
platform has evolved.
And nowhere is that more readily apparent
than here,
at the Android Lawn sculpture garden.
Join me here, at the very heart of
Android, at the end of this lesson,
to find out how this sculpture garden of
tasty treats,
also tell us the story of Android's
history.
For now, let's get back to building that
weather app.
So, we'll cross to Dan, to take a look at
some mocks.