1
00:00:00,440 --> 00:00:02,790
谢谢Raido  有了这种概念之后  让我们
Thanks Raido, with that in mind let's add

2
00:00:02,790 --> 00:00:05,450
在我们的应用上临时的添加一个刷新菜单按钮
a Refresh Menu button to our app. For temporary

3
00:00:05,450 --> 00:00:07,920
目的是去练习使用  否则Raido会和我们生气的
purposes only though, otherwise Raido would be mad at

4
00:00:07,920 --> 00:00:11,882
在Android上  菜单的选项是定义在XML里面的
us. On Android, menu options are defined in XML

5
00:00:11,882 --> 00:00:14,440
而且他们可以在fragments或者是activities里面声明
and they can be declared for fragments or

6
00:00:14,440 --> 00:00:18,390
当fragment或者是activity创建的时候  它会
activities. When the fragment or activity is created, it

7
00:00:18,390 --> 00:00:21,790
在我们的应用中把XML文档变成一个真正的菜单项
inflates this XML into the actual menu items in

8
00:00:21,790 --> 00:00:25,440
你会看到那里有操作按钮
the app. You'll see that there are Action buttons

9
00:00:25,440 --> 00:00:28,230
并且它们在菜单栏中出现 
which are menu items that appear in the Action bar,

10
00:00:28,230 --> 00:00:31,670
比如这个搜索菜单项  这个地方是保留给
such as this Search Menu item. This space is reserved

11
00:00:31,670 --> 00:00:34,550
你的应用中最显著的活动  然后其余不是很重要的菜单项  
for the most prominent actions in your app. Then anything

12
00:00:34,550 --> 00:00:37,990
将会布局到浮动菜单上  
else that's less important falls into the overflow menu by

13
00:00:37,990 --> 00:00:40,790
通过单击这个标记了三个点按钮你就能看到它们
tapping on this button with the three dots. These menu

14
00:00:40,790 --> 00:00:44,560
这些菜单项是按照最常用到最不常用的方式来排序的
items are ordered from most frequently used to least frequently

15
00:00:44,560 --> 00:00:47,550
在大一点的设备上  因为有着更多的屏幕区域  
used. And on larger devices that have more screen real

16
00:00:47,550 --> 00:00:50,710
你可以制定这其中的菜单项  把它们放到
estate, you can specify that some of these menu items can

17
00:00:50,710 --> 00:00:54,120
操作栏里面  如果操作栏还有空间的话
actually go into the Action bar if there's room. If

18
00:00:54,120 --> 00:00:57,160
如果你回过来看下我们项目的资源目录  这里
you go back to our project in the Resources folder

19
00:00:57,160 --> 00:00:59,660
叫做res  这里有一个菜单文件夹  
which is called res, there is a Menu folder and

20
00:00:59,660 --> 00:01:03,990
在里面有一个main.xml的文件  如果你打开这个文件  
inside that there's a main.xml file. If you open that up

21
00:01:03,990 --> 00:01:06,360
你可以看到菜单的布局的XML文档  而在其中
you see the menu layout XML, and that there's a

22
00:01:06,360 --> 00:01:10,130
有一个单独的菜单选项定义在Settings里面  它不会在
single menu option defined for Settings. It will never show up

23
00:01:10,130 --> 00:01:12,350
操作栏里面作为一个操作项来显示  也就是说  
as an action in the Action bar, meaning that it

24
00:01:12,350 --> 00:01:15,780
它会被放在浮动菜单上  你可以通过在手机上查看你的应用
will be in the Overflow menu. You can verify this by

25
00:01:15,780 --> 00:01:18,880
来确定这一点去定义菜单项的顺序  
checking the app on your phone. To define the ordering

26
00:01:18,880 --> 00:01:22,200
你可以加入多个项目到这个XML文件里面  
of menu items, you can just add multiple items to this

27
00:01:22,200 --> 00:01:24,580
然后它们会按照定义过的顺序显示在你的应用里面
XML file, and then they will show up in that order

28
00:01:24,580 --> 00:01:27,680
如果你不喜欢这种顺序  而
in the app. If you don't like the order though, and

29
00:01:27,680 --> 00:01:30,460
你想要明确的设置它们  你可以在
you want to explicitly set it, then you can specify

30
00:01:30,460 --> 00:01:34,030
类别里面指定其顺序  目前的数值设置的是100
this order in Category, value. Right now it's set as 100,

31
00:01:34,030 --> 00:01:37,460
所以设置菜单就会出现在所有的
so that the Settings menu will be at the bottom of

32
00:01:37,460 --> 00:01:40,040
我们在应用中定义的其他的菜单项的最下面
all the other menu options that we define in our app.

33
00:01:41,080 --> 00:01:44,250
而其中只有一个菜单项出现在设置菜单的下面  
The only Menu option that should show up below the Settings

34
00:01:44,250 --> 00:01:47,450
就是帮助菜单  请点击这个链接来了解更多的细节
menu is the Help menu. Check out the link for more details.

