1
00:00:00,280 --> 00:00:02,550
这里是刷新按钮的代码  在
Here's the code for the Refresh button in

2
00:00:02,550 --> 00:00:06,060
forecastfragment菜单的XML文件的部分  我们想让它
the forecastfragment menu XML file. We want it to

3
00:00:06,060 --> 00:00:09,160
出现在浮动菜单上  所以我们把它的showAsAction属性设置
appear in the overflow menu, so we set showAsAction

4
00:00:09,160 --> 00:00:12,280
成为永不  我们这里也声明了一个字符串  你可以
as never. We also declare the string. You can

5
00:00:12,280 --> 00:00:15,560
在string.xml文件中找到这个字符串  这个文件
find the string here in the strings.xml file, which

6
00:00:15,560 --> 00:00:17,810
存放在res目录下面的valuse文件夹中
is located in the values folder, which is in

7
00:00:17,810 --> 00:00:21,230
你可以把你的string.xml文件里面的字符翻译
the res folder. You can get your strings.xml file

8
00:00:21,230 --> 00:00:25,340
成为不同的语言  在res下面  这样可以添加额外的values文件夹
translated into different languages. This adds additional values folders,

9
00:00:25,340 --> 00:00:28,364
比如  你可以这样添加
under Res. For example, you would have

10
00:00:28,364 --> 00:00:33,230
values-es  这是西班牙语  values-fr这是法语  然后
values-es, for Spanish, values-fr for French. And

11
00:00:33,230 --> 00:00:35,450
在每一个values文件夹里面
within each of those values folders, you

12
00:00:35,450 --> 00:00:37,660
都要有一个strings.xml文件  这个文件里面
would have a strings.xml file, which would

13
00:00:37,660 --> 00:00:39,940
包含的是为此类语言进行翻译和改进过的
contain the localized strings for that language.

14
00:00:40,970 --> 00:00:43,170
由于翻译有时候是花钱的  给你一个专业的
Since translation does cost money, as a

15
00:00:43,170 --> 00:00:45,200
提示  你可以把那些
pro tip, you can mark strings that

16
00:00:45,200 --> 00:00:50,210
你不想翻译的字符串标记为translatable=false  举个例子
you don't need translated using translatable=false. For example,

17
00:00:50,210 --> 00:00:53,560
当这如果它是一个合适的名字  或者是仅仅为了调试而存在的
if it's a proper name or if it's for debugging like this one,

18
00:00:53,560 --> 00:00:57,180
那你可以告诉你的翻译员  可以忽略这些字符串的翻译
then you can indicate to the translator that they can skip over this strings

