在平板的网格图中，当一个列表被选择后，
In the tablet wireframes, when a list item is selected
会显示一个蓝色的激活框的背景。通过设置背景的状态
it shows this blue activated state background. This can be done
列表可以被设置成为
by setting the background of the list item to be
可绘型。我们看看文档是怎么在以下说明
a state drawable. We can look at the documentation for the
StateListDrawable 的。
StateListDrawable, which is linked below.
本质上，一个StateListDrawable 可以允许你
Essentially a StateListDrawable allows you
基于不同的界面特别的选出不同的可绘型模板。
to specify different drawables based on the state of the view.
我们提供了StateListDrawable的一些代码。把这些代码
We provide you the code for the StateListDrawable. Drop it in
放进res目录下的一个drawable 文件夹里。
by creating a drawable folder under the res directory. When set
on the background of a list item, the touch selector will
appear transparent by default. As seen here we just see the background
of the activity come through. When the view is pressed then
we see a grey background. Then when the state is activated we
see a blue background. This indicates that it's the selected item
into pay mode. In the list item layout, we set the background
to be this drawable touch selector. We also did the same
for the today layout. In the touch selector file, we also see
that we have some colors defined here. That Android color notation
is for a framework defined color. Our colors are in the colors.xml
file. This is located under the values folder. This us useful
if you need to reference colors multiple times in your app. As
a hint, to make a list item show its activated state,
you can look at the documentation for the XML attribute choice mode
for the list view. Once you find the right attribute, you'll realize
that you want different behavior for one pane versus two pane mode.
While you could change the behavior programmatically in the Java
code, we'd like you to do it purely via the resource
XML files using a style. Read this doc to learn
about how styles can be defined in XML and use what
you learned earlier about defining alternative resources for different sized
devices. In general, styles are a way that you can group
together attributes for a view. For example, these text attributes
are replaced by this style CodeFont. The CodeFont styles is defined
in the styles.xml file, located in the values folder.
You can also have styles inherent other styles by specifying
the parent. There are a couple other examples that you
can check out on this page. This is what the
app should look like when you're done. The two
pane mode shows the pressed and activated state. On the
web pane mode, we see just the press state, because
tapping on an item brings you to the details screen.