Now that's a contract.
At this point, we defined
the names of the columns we want.
But we still don't have a database.
To actually make a database, we're going
to extend Android's SQLiteOpenHelper.
SQLiteOpenHelper contains cool
stuff to create the database and
help us handle database versioning.
As we make changes to our
database in the future,
it will help us modify our tables.
For many apps,
being able to upgrade to a new
version without data loss is critical.
For Sunshine, we just want to make sure
that upgrades that involve database
schema changes happens smoothly.
Let's take a look at SQLiteOpenHelper
more closely in action.
We're going to be working in the
WeatherDBHelper class that you've been
given which extends SQLiteOpenHelper.
It contains code to create and
initialize the weather database.
Let's examine it.
At the beginning of the DBHelper, you
can see that we've defined constants for
database version and database name.
The database version typically starts
at version one, and must be manually
incremented each time we release an
updated ABK with a new database schema.
The database name is the name of the
actual database file in the file system,
which will be weather.db, in our case.
Note that we're using version 2.
Since this revision of the course
uses an updated database version.
These values get passed
into the constructor
to initialize the database helper.
Next we have the on create method.
This is where the SQL we've
been talking about and
our new contract class
are used together.
The first time the database
is used SQLiteOpenHelpers
on create will be called.
We need to write the correct
SQL statement strings so
that we can create
the table Sunshine needs.
We then have the system execute
this SQL by calling db.execSQL.
Note how we're using all of the weather
entry constants to write our
SQL statements.
Also note that we use lots of not
null constraints on this table.
These constraints help prevent us from
inserting records without columns being
filled out to the database and
that helps prevent bugs.
Here is the implementation of the
foreign key constraint from the not yet
created LocationEntry table.
This means that we cannot insert
a WeatherEntry into the database until
a LocationEntry for
the weather location has been inserted.
And we cannot delete
locations while there exists
WeatherEntrys that point to them.
That being said,
it's going to be awhile before we
have UI that can demonstrate that
our database code is working.
Fortunately, there's a way we can
have Android run any code we want,
even if there's no UI yet ready.
Android has a built-in testing framework
that allows us to create a test APK that
executes a JUnit test that call
into classes in our main APK.
If you aren't already
familiar with JUnit,
it is a testing framework that allows
you to write automated test suites.
You can run your automated tests easily.
You can find your tests in this
section of the Android Studio project.
Just right-click on the test package and
select Run.
Once the tests pass or
fail, you'll see the output down
here at the bottom of the screen.
I'm not going to display the emulator
in our screen because it won't actually
show that we're doing anything.
The tests we're running don't
have any user interface.
But you can see here in the test runner,
we're instantiating tests.
An empty window and
a green result means the test succeeded.
Let's look at the TestPractice class.
You can see it sits in the data
package of our TestProject and
extends AndroidTestCase.
When you extend AndroidTestCase,
you can implement the setup method,
which will be run before each test.
You can also implement tearDown
which will be run after each test.
Similar to JUnit test,
you simply add new methods in
the class with the prefix test.
Such as
testThatDemonstrationsAssertions, and
those will automatically be
run by the test processor.
Some other things to note.
The FullTestSuite class contains code
to include all of the java test classes
in its package into a suite
of tests that JUnit will run.
This allows us to easily add additional
tests by just adding additional java
class files to our test directory.
You'll likely have a class like
this in each test project you make.
They aren't typically product specific,
so you can literally just copy this one.
Each test should have at least
one check which uses an assert
to see if the program
supplies the correct output.
And assert is just that, it's a
declaration that the outcome after part
of a test is run matches
our expectation.
If the assert does not match,
the test will fail.
Let's look at our
testThatDemonstratesAssertions
in test practice at java.
A assertEquals asserts that the expected
value equals the actual value.
If they are not equal,
then an assertion fail there is
thrown with a given string message.
Other useful methods include
assertEquals, assertFalse, assertNull.
Or, we can just call fail.
The certain code path should
never have been reached.
Feel free to write your own test
cases to play with assertions.
Let's see what happens
when we make a test fail.
As you can see,
our results are now red, and
we can see exactly where in
the test our application failed.
Let's uncomment out the test create DB
function inside of the TestDb class.
You might have to import a few
classes to get this to compile.
Let's also uncomment out
the createNorthPoleLocationValues, and
the insertNorthPoleLocationValues
functions from within test utilities.
This is the last chance to fix
up your location contract if
things don't compile.
So let's run our new
test with our Testdb.
As you can see, we get a pretty good
error message back, that our database
was created without both the location
entry and weather entry tables.
Don't worry, we can fix it.