When we first defined our tables,
we defined the relationship between
them in terms of constraints.
I'm going to show how we implemented
that relationship into our
query using a join.
This join allows us to
query the weather table for
values from a specific location setting.
In Sunshine's case,
the user sets this in preferences.
You'll notice that there's a SQ
lite query builder class for
able at the top of weather provider.
As you might guess,
this class helps construct queries and
is actually used as the basis for
the query functions you've already
used in the SQLite database class.
We initialize the SQLite query builder
in the static constructor of the class.
Describing the join between both tables.
Set.Tables fills out the content
in the from part of the SQL query.
Note, since both tables
have a field with an _ID,
we must explicitly use the table
name in order to disambiguate
which ID we are talking
about in the join.
Then we define the selection.
The selection is defined using
the question mark or placement syntax.
The selection parameters
will replace these values.
As you can see,
our selection has 2 parameters,
a location setting and a date.
Then we have a function to get the
weather by location setting using this
same query builder.
Note that we fetch
the parameters from the URI.
And build the string array and
build the string array so
that they can be
substituted into our query.
We do that for both of the queries
that we're creating this way.
Finally, we added the functions into the
query routine of the content provider
for both weather with location and
date and weather with location.