Okay.
Now for the big quiz.
Implement the details view
using a CursorLoader.
We've just implemented a CursorLoader
for forecast fragment.
So if you're unsure where to start,
start with the same steps we used for
forecast fragment.
You can use the same
utility functions and
even the same format that we
used in forecast fragment
to help you format the string that
you will set into the detail view.
Consider taking
advantage of projections.
The trickiest part of all this is
making sure that your sharing function
is still working when you're all done.
But don't worry too much about that.
The important thing is to
understand how CursorLoaders work.
Look at the solution if you really
want to see how sharing is done.
If you're at all confused
about how sharing is done,
just look at the solution.