In the ForecastAdapter bindView method,
we have to traverse
the view hierarchy to find the views
in order to set data onto them.
If it's a recycled view,
meaning it's been used in the list
previously to display other data,
we still have to traverse the view
hierarchy to find all the views.
To remove unnecessary
findViewById calls,
we can use the View Holder Pattern.
For a list item layout that
contains different views,
we can create a View Holder object.
It contains member variables that
reference each View in the layout.
The View Holder object is stored
in the tag field of the View.
The next time that
the View is recycled and
used again, we can just immediately
set the data on to these fields.
You don't have to go
find all the views again.
This is our ViewHolder class.
You can name it anything you want.
It's just a Java class.
Given the list item layout,
we do all the findViewById calls.
That way we can hold references
to all the child views.
In the newView method after
we've inflated the view,
we create a new viewHolder
object from that view.
Then we set that viewHolder
as the tag of the view.
The tag can be used to store any object.
But don't abuse it because
when you read it back you,
have to know what you stored in there.
Then in the adaptor bindView call,
we read from the tag to get
back the viewHolder object.
Now we immediately have references to
all the individual views that we need to
update, such as icon view, date view,
description view and so on.